<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Severiano Sisneros&#39; Blog</title>
    <link>https://severiano-sisneros.github.io/website/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Severiano Sisneros&#39; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 19:57:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://severiano-sisneros.github.io/website/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ZkOps: The Future of Zero Knowledge Deployment Tools Panel by Aaron Greenblatt</title>
      <link>https://severiano-sisneros.github.io/website/posts/videos/zkops-the-future-of-zero-knowledge-deployment-tools-panel-by-aaron-greenblatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 19:57:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://severiano-sisneros.github.io/website/posts/videos/zkops-the-future-of-zero-knowledge-deployment-tools-panel-by-aaron-greenblatt/</guid>
      <description>This was a panel I participated in at ETHDenver 2023, chaired by Aaron Greenblatt of Ironmill.
&amp;ldquo;There is great excitement surrounding the potential applications for newly-introduced zero knowledge (zk) proof systems. However, today, there are barriers to mass adoption of zk verifiable computing: zk proof generation involves many end-user mathematical choices; is computationally intense, and; leverages a wide array of software languages and libraries. Accordingly, widespread adoption of zk will require additional practical, operational infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devcon VI: A SNARKs Tale</title>
      <link>https://severiano-sisneros.github.io/website/posts/videos/devcon-vi-a-snarks-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 19:45:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://severiano-sisneros.github.io/website/posts/videos/devcon-vi-a-snarks-tale/</guid>
      <description>This talk was a high level, light on technical detail, description of some our research into various SNARK constructions while designing and building a high-throughput one-way payment channel solution to enable query payments for indexers in The Graph protocol. We looked at several cutting edge SNARKs and also Homomorphic Signatures. In the end, all the verification for all these methods where too high to justify, we ended up engineering a much simpler (cryptographically) system using only standard ECC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
